#### Contact

kat8415@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/katie-burgauer-rn-bsn-bc-b3866076 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Wound Care
Patient Advocacy
Endoscopy

### Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

### Honors-Awards

Cumma Sum Laude

# Katie Burgauer RN, BSN, BC

Registered Nurse at GHR Travel Nursing

Washington D.C. Metro Area

## Summary

Current travel nurse in DC working in the Endoscopy suite as a preop/recovery nurse.

Previously worked as travel nurse on a surgical women's/ gynecological/complicated post partum unit.

Experienced Endoscopy Charge Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the medical practice industry. Skilled in Patient Advocacy, Kronos, Conscious Sedation, Time Management, and Teamwork. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelors in Nursing and a board certification in Med Surg.

## Experience

GHR Travel Nursing Registered Nurse June 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month) Fairfax, Virginia

Surgical/gyn travel RN

**HCA West Florida Careers** 

7 years 1 month

**Endoscopy Charge Nurse** 

November 2017 - Present (2 years 8 months)

Largo, Florida

Compassionate and highly qualified charge endoscopy nurse with experience working hand in hand with physicians. ACLS, PALS, and BLS certified with a BSN. Board certified medical surgical nurse with current expertise in endoscopy nursing. Responsible for department payroll, scheduling, yearly evaluations and competency checks.

**Endoscopy Staff Nurse** 

February 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Largo, Florida

Surgical services nurse working as a nurse circulator in endoscopic procedures including GI procedures, liver/kidney biopsies, TEE, bronchoscopy, pain management injections, blood patches, etc. worked as part of the team rotating weekly and weekend call.

Medical Surgical Nurse June 2013 - February 2016 (2 years 9 months) Largo, Florida

## Education

St. Petersburg College

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2016)

St. Petersburg College

Associates in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2013)

Ivy Tech Community College

· (2009 - 2011)